General Guidelines: 
use relative path
code should be reusable
please save code script in the code folder, temp files in tmp folder, and output in the output folder when done
write a readme if the program requires extra instructions to be run (ie when I check, please let me know anything extra i need to do other than runing your code directly in order to get the same output as you delivered)


Input: 
everything in folder input > "700d"
note:those docs w same names but both in .xlsx and .csv are actually same file
You need to make sure that all the files indeed have the same number of columns in the same order and it'd be good to automate this checking step as part of the code as well.

Task:
交易记录都合并成一个文挡, 去掉当中全部的重复条目. Py 程序 请确保code能够以后重复使用
hint: in the code file, there is a file that shows you how to merge all csv files with the same heading into one csv. If you don't understand or cannot figure out how to run it, write your own code instead.

Output:
The main output file "700d_transrec_combined.txt" should be saved as .txt with utf-8 bom encoding. 
(hint: to accomplish this, you may use notepad++ (a free software) to convert encoding)

Additionally, you should have a second output file "700d_transrec_item_id.csv" that returns the unique item_ids from the main output.